

THAI THI YEN NHI Front-end Developer

nhithai88@gmail.com +84 974 833 783 nhidev.netlify.com

With a strong technical skill-set, attention to detail, and 4+ years of experience, I want to work as a front-end web developer where I could create digital magic and elevate user experience to the next level.

Experience

REDWEB

Front-end Developer

09/2017 - 06/2018 redweb.vn

- Create, modify websites using Joomla CMS and our ecommerce platform.
- Upgrade client sites (Ecommerce platform, Joomla CMS).
- Fix front end related bugs that were identified in QA, beta and production environments.
- Attend wire frame review, design and html code walkthrough meetings.

1PAC

Front-end Developer

08/2016 - 06/2017 1pac.vn

- Develop HTML/CSS templates from Photoshop visual design and wireframes.
- Refactor code and delivering products with high quality, write code that runs cross browsers.
- Research trending technologies and apply it to real production.

CANON LE BAO MINH

Web Developer

05/2014 - 07/2016 lebaominh.vn

- Create, modify websites using WordPress CMS.
- Used jquery to build accordion style content, drag and drop functionality, calendar, popup and modal windows
- Cross-browser compatible by writing W3C validated Semantic XHTML.
- Responsible for solving page layout issues.
- Monitored the web analysis reports to view the performance of the company websites.

Skills

HTML	CSS	SCSS	JavaScript	Bootstrap	jQı	uery	ReactJS	Grunt
Joomla	Wordpress		Photoshop	Github	Jira			

Education

Bachelor of Science from Hutech University (2013)

Associate of Science from Hoa Sen University (2009)

Language

English (intermediate)